Finding Aid for News and Information Services (University of Michigan) photograph series D (faculty and staff portraits), 1946-2006
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Series D, Faculty and Staff Portraits
  - H
    - Heppingstall, Robert S., Engineering Drawing, 1960 (Box 6)
    - Hepworth, Samuel, Accounting, 1969 (Box 6)
    - Herbert, Ralph, Music, 1963 (Box 6)
    - Herlinger, Paul, Broadcasting, 1956 (Box 6)
    - Hermalin, Jolene, Music, 1982 (Box 6)
    - Herman, Claudia (SEE: Hopwood Winners), Hopwood Winner (Box 6)
    - Herman, Donald, English, College of Engineering, 1960 (Box 6)
    - Herold, J. Downs, IST, 1976 (Box 6)
    - Herrick, Paul, Bureau of Industrial Relations, 1966 (Box 6)
    - Herrick, Theral, Economic Education, 1965 (Box 6)
    - Herrin, Gary D., Industrial and Operations Engineering, 1978 (Box 6)
    - Herrington, NROTC, 1967 (Box 6)
    - Hertz, Elsa, 1962 (Box 6)
    - Hertzler, Emanuel C., Biology (Box 6)
    - Herzog, Bertram, Engineering Mechanics, 1961, 1976 (Box 6)
    - Herzog, Donald, 1987 (Box 6)
    - Hess, Robert L., Engineering Mechanics, 1955, 1968, 1975 (Box 6)
    - Hesseltine, Douglas H., University Relations, 1977 (Box 6)
    - Heusel, Albert, Security, 1952 (Box 6)
    - Hewson, E. Wendell, Civil Engineering, 1957, 1960, 1955 (Box 6)
      (na 688)
    - Heyer, Paul, Architecture and Design, 1961 (Box 6)
    - Heyns, Roger, VP for Academic Affairs, 1963 (Box 6)
    - Heytler, Peter, 1983 (Box 6)
    - Hiatt, Ralph E., Electrical Engineering, 1962, 1973, 1978 (Box 6)
    - Hibbard, Claude W., 1951 (Box 6)
    - Hickey, Tom, Health Behavior/Health Ed., 1989, 1985, 1978 (Box 6)
    - Hickman, Harold C., Plant Service, 1957 (Box 6)
    - Hicks, Aubrey B., Sponsored Research Business Office, 1963 (Box 6)
    - Higgins, George, BIR, 1967 (Box 6)
    - Higgins, Ian T., Epidemiology, 1969 (Box 6)
    - Higham, John, History, 1971, 1963 (Box 6)
    - Hilbert, Morton S., Environmental and Industrial Health, 1974, 1963 (Box 6)
    - Hilbish, Thomas, Music, 1969, 1979, 1970 (Box 6)
    - Hildebrandt, Herbert W., Speech, 1967, 1966, 1981, 1975 (Box 6)
    - Hile, Lulu M., Business Administration, 1955 (Box 6)
    - Hile, Ralph, U.S. Bureau of Commerical Fisheries; Natural Resources, 1961 (Box 6)
    - Hilgenberg, Katherine, Music, 1970 (Box 6)
    - Hill, Cary L., Natural Resources, 1959 (Box 6)
      (na 637)
    - Hill, Donald L., English, 1960 (Box 6)
    - Hill, Geoffrey W., English, 1960 (Box 6)
    - Hill, L. Clayton, Industrial Relations, 1955 (Box 6)
      (na 690)
    - Hill, Lawrence A., Hospital Administration, 1963 (Box 6)
    - Hill, Raymond, Business Administration, 1973 (Box 6)
    - Hillegas, Mark R., English, 1959 (Box 6)
    - Hiltner, William A., Astronomy and Physics, 1970 (Box 6)
    - Hilton, James, Psychology, 1997, 1999 (Box 6)
    - Himeno, Yoji, Engineering, 1978 (Box 6)
    - Himes, Harold, Architecture, 1965, 1973 (Box 6)
    - Himler, Leonard, Mental Health, 1963 (Box 6)
    - Hinchey, M. Catherine, Zoology, 1968, 1967 (Box 6)
    - Hinds, Richard J., University Hospital, 1962 (Box 6)
    - Hinken, Ed. M., 1955 (Box 6)
    - Hinshaw, Ada Sue, Nursing, 1999, 1994 (Box 6)
    - Hisey, James H., Business Administration, 1969 (Box 6)
    - Hiss, Roland, 1967 (Box 6)
    - Hitchcock, H. Wiley, Music, 1950, 1958 (Box 6)
    - Hoad, William C., Small Business, 1958 (Box 6)
    - Hoag (Box 6)
    - Hobart, Dean E., Engineering, 1961 (Box 6)
    - Hobbs, Chief, Naval Science, 1965 (Box 6)
    - Hobbs, William H., 1950 (Box 6)
    - Hoch, Erasmus, Psychology, 1965 (Box 6)
    - Hodgdon, P. L., NROTC, 1966 (Box 6)
    - Hodges, Lewis H., Vocational Education, 1957, 1955, 1972 (Box 6)
      (na 648)
    - Hodkinson, Sydney, Music, 1967, 1970 (Box 6)
    - Hoffman, Lois, Research Center for Group Dynamics; Public Health, 1957, 1972 (Box 6)
    - Hoffmeyer, Dorothy, Survey Research Center, 1961 (Box 6)
    - Hoisington, Robert H., Engineering (Box 6)
    - Hok, Gunnar, Engineering, 1959 (Box 6)
    - Hok, Ruth, English Language Institute, 1963 (Box 6)
    - Holbrook, Robert S., Vice President for Academic Affairs; Economics, 1991, 1988 (Box 6)
    - Holcombe, Warne C., English, College of Engineering, 1960 (Box 6)
    - Holland, John H., Institute of Science and Technology, 1971 (Box 6)
    - Holland, Lewis N., Electrical Engineering, 1960 (Box 6)
    - Holland, William J., Health Service, 1957 (Box 6)
      (na 691)
    - Hollbrook, Diane, 1952 (Box 6)
    - Hollinger, David A., History, 1982 (Box 6)
    - Hollingsworth, Peggie, Pharmacology, 1989, 1981, 1987, 1988, 1982, 1984 (Box 6)
    - Hollstein, Roy, Engineering (Box 6)
    - Holmes, James, Business Administration, 1966 (Box 6)
    - Holmes, Robert B., Vice President for Academic Affairs, 1995, 1993, 1982 (Box 6)
    - Holmgren, Nelda, Epidemiology, 1963 (Box 6)
    - Holmquist, Barbara, 1964 (Box 6)
    - Holton, Raymond, Botany, Flint Senior College, 1957 (Box 6)
    - Holtz, William V., English, College of Engineering, 1960 (Box 6)
    - Holz, Emil A., Music, 1960, 1970 (Box 6)
    - Holz, James N., Finance, 1960 (Box 6)
    - Hood, Marguerite, Music, 1966 (Box 6)
    - Hooper, Emmet T., Zoology, 1966, 1956 (Box 6)
    - Hooper, Frank, 1966 (Box 6)
    - Hooven, Betty, Business Administration, 1960 (Box 6)
    - Hopkins, Louis A., 1950 (Box 6)
    - Hopwood Winners (Box 6)
    - Hord, Robert W., Music, 1956, 1972, 1976 (Box 6)
    - Horn, Barbara, Public Health, 1971 (Box 6)
    - Hornback, Bert, English, 1977 (Box 6)
    - Horwitch, Matthew W. (Box 6)
    - Hosford, William F., Jr., Metallurgical Engineering, 1963, 1983, 1977 (Box 6)
    - Hosmer, Larue T., Business Administration, 1986, 1980 (Box 6)
    - Hotra, Nancy, Pharmacy, 1973 (Box 6)
    - Hough, Jack, Oceanography, 1964 (Box 6)
    - Hough, Maxine L., Bureau of School Services, 1972 (Box 6)
    - Hourani, George, Islamic History and Philosophy, 1966 (Box 6)
    - House, Clyde M., Extension Service, 1959 (Box 6)
    - House, James S., Sociology, 1986, 1978 (Box 6)
    - Housel, William S., Civil Engineering (Box 6)
    - Howard, Ken, Housing E.O.M., 1992 (Box 6)
    - Howard, William E. III, Astronomy, 1960 (Box 6)
    - Howell, Robert, Philosophy, 1965 (Box 6)
    - Howell, Roger, Mental Health, 1963 (Box 6)
    - Howes, Alan B., English, 1959 (Box 6)
    - Howland, R. S., 1948 (Box 6)
    - Hseih, hsung, cheng, 1964 (Box 6)
    - Hubbard, William N., Jr., Medical School, 1960 (Box 6)
    - Hubbell, Theodore H., Zoology, 1966, 1948 (Box 6)
    - Hubler, Charles, 1964 (Box 6)
    - Hucke, Edward E., Metallurgical Engineering, 1964, 1975, 1977 (Box 6)
    - Hucker, Charles O., Chinese and History (Box 6)
    - Huebner, Gertrude, Regent, 1971 (Box 6)
    - Huelke, Donald, Medical School, 1968, 1966, 1962, 1971 (Box 6)
    - Huetteman, E. Jude, 1973 (Box 6)
    - Hughes, Byron O., School of Education; School of Dentistry; University School, 1957 (Box 6)
    - Hughes, David, Engineering English (Box 6)
    - Hughes, Lloyd, Education, 1975 (Box 6)
    - Hughes, Robert, Housing, 1988, 1985, 1983, 1977 (Box 6)
    - Huh, Kyung Mo, Economics, 1963 (Box 6)
    - Hulslander, Stewart C., Education, 1953 (Box 6)
    - Hultquist, Donald, 1967 (Box 6)
    - Hunsicker, Paul A., Education, 1962, 1955, 1975, 1970 (Box 6)
      (na 696)
    - Hunt, George, Natural Resources, 1957 (Box 6)
    - Hunt, Jim, Physical Education and Athletics, 1968 (Box 6)
    - Hunt, Marian, Music, 1976 (Box 6)
    - Hunt, Walter F., 1951 (Box 6)
    - Hunter, Sandra, Housing, 1986 (Box 6)
    - Hunter, Woodrow W., Division of Gerontology, 1965 (Box 6)
    - Huntley, Frank L., English, 1957, 1946 (Box 6)
    - Hurd, Russell, Naval Science, 1964 (Box 6)
    - Hurst, Lawrence, Music, 1964 (Box 6)
    - Hurtado, Sylvia, 1992 (Box 6)
    - Hurwitz, Jacob, 1951 (Box 6)
    - Huskey, Dorothy, Public Health, 1963 (Box 6)
    - Hussey, Russell, Geology, 1963 (Box 6)
    - Hutchcroft, C. Robert, Education, 1975 (Box 6)
    - Hutchinson, Richard, Benefits, 1964 (Box 6)
    - Hutt, Max L., Psychology, 1947 (Box 6)
    - Hyde, John W., Planning, 1950 (Box 6)
      (na 698)
    - Hydeman, Lee M., Law, 1958, 1959 (Box 6)
    - Hyer, Paul, 1963 (Box 6)
    - Hyland, David C., Aerospace Engineering, 1996 (Box 6)
    - Hylton, Lydia, Social Work, 1959 (Box 6)
      (nb 355)
    - Hyma, Albert, History, 1962, 1952 (Box 6)
      (na 699)
    - Hymans, Saul H., Economics, 1972, 1984, 1977 (Box 6)
    - Hymovitch, Bernard, Institute for Human Adjustment (Box 6)
      (na 656)
  - I
    - Icerman, Paul F., Accounting, 1957, 1954 (Box 6)
      (na 700, nb 390)
    - Iglehart, Rober L., Art, 1963, 1955 (Box 6)
      (na 700)
    - Im, Hong, Mechanical Engineering (Box 6)
    - Imhoff, Eugene, Accounting, 1980, 1985 (Box 6)
    - Ingalls, J. Peter (SEE: Hopwood Winners), Hopwood Winner (Box 6)
    - Ingram, Eugene O., 1968 (Box 6)
    - Ingram, Winigred, Children's Service, 1955 (Box 6)
      (na 658)
    - Irwin, James, Speech, 1984, 1966 (Box 6)
    - Irwin, Millie, 1984 (Box 6)
    - Isaacson, Robert L., Psychology, 1960 (Box 6)
    - Isakson, Gabriel, Aeronautical Engineering, 1961 (Box 6)
    - Isbell, Mary D. Carter, Library Science, 1960 (Box 6)
    - Islam, Zafar U., History, 1961 (Box 6)
    - Israel, Jerold H., Law, 1972, 1971, 1964 (Box 6)
  - J
    - Jackson, Charles, Division of Adult Education, 1962 (Box 6)
    - Jackson, James, Psych., 1973 (Box 6)
    - Jackson, Jay M., Survey Research Center; Psychology, 1957 (Box 6)
    - Jackson, John E., Political Science, 1984 (Box 6)
    - Jackson, John H., Law, 1977 (Box 6)
    - Jackson, Mame (Marion), History of Art, 1981, 1984, 1973 (Box 6)
    - Jackson, Marjorie M., Nursing, 1980 (Box 6)
    - Jackson, Murray, Higher Education, 1983 (Box 6)
    - Jackson, Philip, Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1978 (Box 6)
    - Jacobi, Roger E., Music, 1963 (Box 6)
    - Jacobs, Pat, Housing E.O.M., 1989 (Box 6)
    - Jacobs, Stanley, Oceanography, 1964 (Box 6)
    - Jacobs, William, Intercollegiate Athletics, 1976 (Box 6)
    - Jacobson, Gene, ISR, 1955 (Box 6)
    - Jacobson, Harold, Political Science, 1957, 1969, 1995, 1974, 1983 (Box 6)
    - Jacobson, Harvey, University Relations, 1974 (Box 6)
    - Jacobson, Patricia, Extension Service, 1973 (Box 6)
    - Jacquez, John, Biostatistics, 1963 (Box 6)
    - Jain, Ramesh, Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1983 (Box 6)
    - James, Donald, 1966 (Box 6)
    - Jameson, Harriet, Library, 1959 (Box 6)
    - Jamison, Charles L., Business Policy, 1949 (Box 6)
      (na 662)
    - Janjanin, Peggy, Housing E.O.M., 1990 (Box 6)
    - Janowitz, Morris, Sociology, 1959 (Box 6)
    - Jay, Leslie, Education, Geography and Extension Service, 1962 (Box 6)
    - Jay, Phillip, Dentistry, 1953 (Box 6)
    - Jeffrey, Randsom, 1969 (Box 6)
    - Jelinek, Arthur, Museum of Anthropology; Anthropology, 1963 (Box 6)
    - Jelinek, Jerome, Music, 1960, 1968 (Box 6)
    - Jelinek, Richard, Industrial Engineering; Hospital Administration, 1965 (Box 6)
    - Jellema, William W., Higher Education; Center for the Study of Higher Ed., 1963 (Box 6)
    - Jenkins, David H., 1951 (Box 6)
    - Jenkins, David R., Engineering Mechanics, 1960 (Box 6)
    - Jenkins, Herbert T., Engineering Drawing, 1960 (Box 6)
    - Jenkins, Janice, Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1983 (Box 6)
    - Jenkins, William A., Dearborn Chancellor, 1980 (Box 6)
    - Jennings, Jack R., Aeronautical Engineering, 1960 (Box 6)
    - Jennings, M. Kent, Political Science, 1968 (Box 6)
    - Jennings, Richard H., Art, 1960 (Box 6)
    - Jensen, Einer, English, 1996, 1994, 1990, 1983 (Box 6)
    - Jensen, Gale E., Education, 1962 (Box 6)
    - Jensen, Jack, 1949 (Box 6)
    - Jeserich, Paul H., Dentistry; Kellog Foundation Institute, 1958 (Box 6)
      (na 703)
    - Jessye, Eva (Box 6)
    - Ji, Jin, Eng. Dept., 1990 (Box 6)
    - Jochim, Kenneth, Physiology, 1963, 1975 (Box 6)
    - Johe, Herbert, Architecture, 1964, 1973 (Box 6)
    - Johns, Andrea, ISR, 1997 (Box 6)
    - Johnson, Arthur G., Bacteriology, 1959 (Box 6)
    - Johnson, Benjamin, Epidemiology, 1963 (Box 6)
    - Johnson, Bruce, Civil Engineering, 1968 (Box 6)
    - Johnson, Carl, Landscape Architecture, 1966 (Box 6)
    - Johnson, Cary, Pharmacy, 1973 (Box 6)
    - Johnson, Charles, English Language Institute, 1963 (Box 6)
    - Johnson, Clyde, Industrial Engineering, 1959 (Box 6)
    - Johnson, Harold, Social Work, 1970, 1993, 1978, 1995, 1987, 1990, 1988, 1979, 1983, 1975 (Box 7)
    - Johnson, Helen, Biostatistics, 1963 (Box 7)
    - Johnson, Henry, VP Student Affairs, 1982, 1987, 1977, 1972 (Box 7)
    - Johnson, Karen, 1995 (Box 7)
    - Johnson, Lemuel A., English Language and Literature, 1981 (Box 7)
    - Johnson, Leonard, Men's Glee Club, 1975 (Box 7)
    - Johnson, Margaret M., Attorney's Office, 1970 (Box 7)
    - Johnson, Michael, 1987 (Box 7)
    - Johnson, William J., Landscape Architecture, 1958, 1968, 1966 (Box 7)
    - Johnston, Bruce G., Structural Engineering, 1957 (Box 7)
    - Johnston, Joseph, Education, 1964 (Box 7)
    - Johnston, Lloyd, ISR, 1997, 1992, 1981 (Box 7)
    - Joiner, Charles, Law, 1964 (Box 7)
    - Jolly, William, 1971 (Box 7)
    - Jones, Dallas, Industrial Relations, 1966 (Box 7)
    - Jones, David L., Meterology, 1958, 1960 (Box 7)
    - Jones, Dorothy E., Institute Labor and Industrial Relations, 1981 (Box 7)
    - Jones, Elodia L., Engineering, 1962 (Box 7)
    - Jones, George, Biological Sciences, 1981 (Box 7)
    - Jones, Howard R., Education, 1961 (Box 7)
    - Jones, J. Wayne, Engineering, 1999, 1978 (Box 7)
    - Jones, John D., Radiation Control Service, 1960 (Box 7)
    - Jones, Kenneth L., Botany, 1962, 1951 (Box 7)
      (na 707)
    - Jones, Lawrence W., Physics, 1979 (Box 7)
    - Jones, Leslie M., UMRI, 1960 (Box 7)
    - Jones, Philip S., Mathematics; Education, 1964, 1952 (Box 7)
      (na 708)
    - Jones, Robert A., Law, 1978 (Box 7)
    - Jones, Roger M., English, College of Engineering, 1960 (Box 7)
    - Jones, Sidney, Finance, 1966 (Box 7)
    - Jorgensen, Joseph, Anthropology, 1972 (Box 7)
    - Joy, William, Public Health Engineering, 1963 (Box 7)
    - Judge, Richard, Medical School, 1968 (Box 7)
    - Julin, Joseph R., Law, 1968, 1970, 1959 (Box 7)
    - Julius, Mara M., Public Health, 1974 (Box 7)
    - Jung, Charles, ISR, 1966 (Box 7)
    - Juster, J. Thomas, ISR, 1975, 1980 (Box 7)
    - Juvinall, Robert C., Mechanical Engineering and Phys Med and Rehab, 1971, 1978, 1982, 1960 (Box 7)
  - K
    - Kachel, A. Theodore, Office of Religious Affairs, 1973 (Box 7)
    - Kadlec, John A., Natural Resources, 1971 (Box 7)
    - Kadlec, Robert, Chemical Engineering, 1961, 1976, 1971, 1974 (Box 7)
    - Kahan, Michael, Survey Research Center, 1966 (Box 7)
    - Kahn, Douglas, Law, 1964, 1989, 1975 (Box 7)
    - Kahn, Peter, Electrical Engineering, 1970 (Box 7)
    - Kahn, Raymond, Medical School, 1972, 1960, 1976 (Box 7)
    - Kahn, Robert L., Psychology, 1956, 1985, 1973 (Box 7)
      (na 709-710)
    - Kaldjian, Movses J., Engineering Mechanics, 1960 (Box 7)
    - Kallenbach, Joseph E., Political Science, 1962 (Box 7)
    - Kallick, Maureen, ISR, 1977 (Box 7)
    - Kalmbach, Robert E., Information Ser., 1978 (Box 7)
    - Kamerick, Maureen, 1974 (Box 7)
    - Kamisar, Yale, Law, 1973, 1965, 1976, 1981, 1979 (Box 7)
    - Kammash, Terry, Nuclear Engineering, 1973, 1960, 1983, 1985, 1977 (Box 7)
    - Kamrowski, Jerome, Drawing and Painting, 1950 (Box 7)
      (na 712)
    - Kanisto, Sue, Alumni Office, 1971 (Box 7)
    - Kaplan, Abraham, Philosophy, 1964 (Box 7)
    - Kaplan, Max (Box 7)
    - Kaplan, Stephen, Psychology, 1966 (Box 7)
    - Kaplan, Wilfred, Mathematics, 1959, 1983 (Box 7)
    - Kardos, Carol J., English, 1959 (Box 7)
    - Karlin, Barry, Center for Population Planning, 1969 (Box 7)
    - Karlstrom, Sten, Bureau of Psychological Services, 1965 (Box 7)
    - Karp, Richard, 1964 (Box 7)
    - Karsen, M., Business Administration, 1967 (Box 7)
    - Kasdin, Robert, Chief Financial Officer, 1998 (Box 7)
    - Kasl, Stanley, ISR, 1968 (Box 7)
    - Katehi, Linda, Engineering, 1999 (Box 7)
    - Katona, George, Psychology; Economics; Survey Research Center, 1958, 1971, 1976 (Box 7)
    - Katona, Mrs. George (Box 7)
    - Katz, Daniel, Psychology; Survey Research Center, 1961, 1975 (Box 7)
    - Katz, Donald L., Chemical Engineering, 1960, 1956, 1967, 1976 (Box 7)
    - Katz, Lee, Academic Affairs, Dearborn, 1975 (Box 7)
    - Kaufman, Irving, Art, Architecture and Design, 1956 (Box 7)
      (na 714)
    - Kaufmann, Berwind P., Zoology, 1966 (Box 7)
    - Kauper, Paul G., Law, 1961, 1969 (Box 7)
    - Kauper, Thomas, Law, 1968 (Box 7)
    - Kaviany, Massoud, M.E.A.M., 1993 (Box 7)
    - Kaye, Orin, 1963 (Box 7)
    - Kayo, B. J., 1968 (Box 7)
    - Kazarionoff, Nicholas D., Mathematics, 1962 (Box 7)
    - Kazda, Louis F., Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1973, 1968, 1965 (Box 7)
    - Kazemzadeh, Firuz (Box 7)
    - Kebschull, Herbert, Naval Science, 1965 (Box 7)
    - Keedy, Hugh, Engineering Mechanics, 1964 (Box 7)
    - Keel, Roger, Naval Science, 1964 (Box 7)
    - Keeler, Gerald, Environmental and Industrial Health, 1994 (Box 7)
    - Keeler, Hugh E., Mechanical Engineering, 1961 (Box 7)
    - Keen, Charles, Education, 1975 (Box 7)
    - Keen, Cliff, Wrestling, 1948, 1965 (Box 7)
      (na 719, nb 401)
    - Keene, James F., Bands, 1973 (Box 7)
    - Kegeles, S. Stephen, Public Health Administration, 1963 (Box 7)
    - Kehoe, John D., General Counsel, 1987 (Box 7)
    - Kehoe, Ray E., Bureau of School Services; Education, 1962, 1967, 1953 (Box 7)
      (na 720)
    - Kell, Walter G., Accounting, 1971 (Box 7)
    - Keller, Leonard A., 1951 (Box 7)
    - Keller, Robert B., Mechanical Engineering, 1962 (Box 7)
    - Kelly, E. Lowell, Psychology; Bureau of Psychological Services, 1949, 1966, 1953 (Box 7)
      (na 722)
    - Kelly, William C., Geology, 1961 (Box 7)
      (nb 403)
    - Kelman, Herbert, Psychology, 1965 (Box 7)
    - Kelsey, Charles, Dentistry, 1968 (Box 7)
    - Kelso, Robert W., Social Work, 1948 (Box 7)
    - Keltner, Shirley, NROTC, 1966 (Box 7)
    - Kemmelmeier, Markus, 1998 (Box 7)
    - Kempe, Lloyd L., Chemical Engineering, 1960 (Box 7)
    - Kemph, John, Psychiatry, 1965 (Box 7)
    - Kendrick, Pearl, Epidemiology, 1964, 1959 (Box 7)
    - Keniston, Hayward, Dean, 1948, 1949 (Box 7)
    - Keniston, Roberta C. (Box 7)
    - Kennedy, Charles S., Regent, 1954 (Box 7)
    - Kennedy, Frank, Law, 1968 (Box 7)
    - Kennedy, Richard L., Development Council, 1960, 1978, 1961, 1964, 1974, 1973, 1980, 1984 (Box 7)
    - Kenyon, Herbert A., 1951 (Box 7)
    - Kering, Dorothy J., Nursing, 1963 (Box 7)
    - Kerlikowske, Albert C., University Hospital (Box 7)
    - Kern, Alice, 1964, 1952 (Box 7)
      (na 727)
    - Kerns, Robert, 1953 (Box 7)
    - Kesling, Robert V., 1951 (Box 7)
    - Kessel, Philip G., Engineering Mechanics, 1961 (Box 7)
    - Ketchum, Warren A., Education, 1953, 1968 (Box 7)
      (na 729)
    - Keuper, Harold, 1966 (Box 7)
    - Khargonekar, Pramod, EECS, 1991 (Box 7)
    - Kiddle, Lawrence B., Spanish (Box 7)
    - Kidston, Roger (Box 7)
    - Kikuchi, Chihiro, Nuclear Engineering, 1965, 1975, 1980, 1983 (Box 7)
    - Kilgour, Raymond L., Library Science, 1960 (Box 7)
    - Kilpatrick, Dee, Social Work, 1973 (Box 7)
    - Kim, Jong, 1956 (Box 7)
    - Kimball, Dick, Athletic Dept., 1960 (Box 7)
    - Kimball, Orville, Engineering, 1966, 1971 (Box 7)
    - Kimball, Spencer L., Law, 1959 (Box 7)
    - Kimbell, Stephen W., Hayden House, 1969 (Box 7)
    - Kimeldorf, Howard, Sociology, 1998 (Box 7)
    - Kimes, Stanley, Music (Box 7)
    - King, Dennis, 1964 (Box 7)
      (na 418)
    - King, Harold V., English, 1968, 1973 (Box 7)
    - King, John S., Nuclear Engineering, 1960 (Box 7)
    - Kingsmith, Eric A., Aerospace Engineering, 1966 (Box 7)
    - Kinnear, Tom, Marketing, 1988 (Box 7)
    - Kipke, Harry G. (Box 7)
    - Kirk, Dudley, Population Council (Box 7)
    - Kirkpatrick, Diane, Art History, 1990, 1980 (Box 7)
    - Kirkpatrick, Susan, Parking and Moving Operations, 1991 (Box 7)
    - Kirschner, Seymour, Environmental Health, 1963 (Box 7)
    - Kirscht, John, Public Health, 1972 (Box 7)
    - Kish, George, Geography, 1974, 1986 (Box 7)
    - Kish, Leslie, Sociology; Survey Research Center, 1961, 1977, 1979, 1971 (Box 7)
    - Kivelson, Valerie Ann, History, 1997 (Box 7)
    - Kjelsberg, Marcus, Biostatistics, 1963 (Box 7)
    - Klaasen, Donald, Administrative Services, Dearborn, 1966, 1971 (Box 7)
    - Klaver, Peter R., English, College of Engineering, 1960 (Box 7)
    - Kleiman, Stephen, 1973 (Box 7)
    - Klein, Maynard, Music, 1963, 1949 (Box 7)
      (na 736)
    - Kleinsmith, Lewis, Zoology, 1971 (Box 7)
    - Kleinsteuck, Miss, 1950 (Box 7)
    - Kline, F. Gerald, Journalism, 1971, 1973 (Box 7)
    - Kluck, David, Housing E.O.M., 1986 (Box 7)
    - Kluge, Arnold G., Zoology, 1966 (Box 7)
    - Kluger, Matthew, Physiology, 1975 (Box 7)
    - Knapp, Greg, Conferences and Seminars Dept., 1992, 1991 (Box 7)
    - Knappen, Marshall, WUOM, 1954 (Box 7)
    - Knauss, Robert L., Law; Student Services, 1960, 1957, 1970, 1971 (Box 7)
      (na 739)
    - Kneer, Walter, Plant, 1957 (Box 7)
      (na 740, na 744)
    - Knepp, Marilyn, Provost, 1997 (Box 7)
    - Knight, Fred B., Forestry, 1965, 1972 (Box 7)
    - Knitzer, Joseph, Music, 1964 (Box 7)
    - Knoll, Glenn F., Nuclear Engineering, 1962, 1973, 1983 (Box 7)
    - Knott, John, English, 1989, 1973, 1980 (Box 7)
    - Knox, James, 1963 (Box 7)
    - Knox, W. John (SEE: Hopwood Winners), Hopwood Winner (Box 7)
    - Koch, Harlan C., Education; Horace H. Rackham School of Graduate Studies, 1959 (Box 7)
    - Kochen, Manfred, 1985 (Box 7)
    - Koen, Frank, Psychology, 1965 (Box 7)
    - Koepke, George H., Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 1959 (Box 7)
    - Koester, Richard P., Cashier, 1959 (Box 7)
    - Kohl, John C., Transportation Institute, 1960 (Box 7)
    - Kolars, John, Geography, 1965 (Box 7)
    - Kole, Larry, Engineering, 1967 (Box 7)
    - Kollens, John L., 1972 (Box 7)
    - Konigsberg, Ira, English Language and Literature; Film/Video Studies, 1988 (Box 7)
    - Konlande, James, Nutrition, 1972 (Box 7)
    - Koops, John B., Bureau of School Services (Box 7)
    - Kopplin, David, 1969 (Box 7)
    - Korn, Harold, Psychology; Office of Student Services, 1982 (Box 7)
    - Kornbluh, Hyman, Education, 1977 (Box 7)
    - Kornegay, Francis, 1973 (Box 7)
    - Korns, Robert, 1955 (Box 7)
    - Kosmensky, Paul, Journalism, 1971 (Box 7)
    - Kosobud, Richard F., Economics; Survey Research Center, 1964 (Box 7)
    - Kotowicz, William E., Dental School, 1990, 1987, 1999 (Box 7)
    - Kottak, Conrad, 1990 (Box 7)
    - Kowalewski, Henry, Architecture, 1973, 1965 (Box 7)
    - Kozma, Robert, Education, 1986, 1979 (Box 7)
    - Krachenberg, Anthony R., Marketing, 1960 (Box 7)
    - Kraft, Richard, 1967 (Box 7)
    - Krahmalkov, Charles R., Ancient Near East Languages, 1974 (Box 7)
    - Krahnke, Geeta, Linguistics, 1969 (Box 7)
    - Krainer, Robert, Business Administration, 1963 (Box 7)
    - Krantz, David, Psych., 1973 (Box 7)
    - Krasny, Robert, Mathematics, 1991 (Box 7)
    - Kraus, Edward H., Crystallography and Minerology, 1961 (Box 7)
    - Kreidler, Charles W., English, 1960 (Box 7)
    - Kreinin, Max, Institute for Social Research, 1955 (Box 7)
    - Krider, James, 1969 (Box 7)
    - Krimm, Samuel, Physics, 1959, 1972 (Box 7)
    - Krislov, Marvin, General Counsel, 1998 (Box 7)
    - Krooth, Robert S., Human Genetics, 1963 (Box 7)
    - Krumm, William B. (Bill), Financial Operations, 1988, 1995 (Box 7)
    - Kruska, H. J., 1947 (Box 7)
    - Kruzas, Anthony, Library Science, 1965 (Box 7)
    - Krystall, Harry, 1965 (Box 7)
      (nb 425)
    - Kuenzel, Franklin C., Michigan Union, 1947 (Box 7)
      (na 747)